vivrussia.nl 2012-12-26

# Privacystatement - VIV Russia

**Personal Information**   
We will ask you for personal information if you wish to use certain services, such as the purchase of exhibition tickets, participation in seminars and use of certain on-line functionalities. 

VNU Exhibitions Europe BV collects this information in a database.  The information is used to execute the services selected by you such as sending out visitor’s badges, exhibition programmes or newsletters.  We may also use your personal information to keep you informed of other exhibitions and events organised by VNU Exhibitions Europe BV.  If you do not wish to receive any information about other activities of VNU Exhibitions Europe BV you may indicate so when submitting your personal information.

We will not share your personal information with third parties without your consent.   If, however, you wish to receive information from exhibitors or other partners selected by us you may indicate so when submitting your personal information. 

Besides the information provided by you we will gather information on your visits to our events.  We do this to adapt our events to the preferences of our visitors where possible and to provide you with relevant information if you so wish.

By giving us personal information upon scanning your badge or otherwise (for instance when you visit a booth, register for a specific lecture/activity, attend an activity or download white papers), you agree that the party(ies) concerned may contact you.  This applies also if you submit your personal information to gain access to specific information or functionalities on our websites.

**Click Behaviour**   
VNU Exhibitions Europe BV gathers general information on the visitors to its websites, such as the number of visitors and the number of clicks on certain pages. 

**Cookies**   
In addition VNU Exhibitions Europe B.V.  can automatically gather information by means of so-called cookies.  VNU Exhibitions Europe B.V. uses cookies to analyse visitor behaviour, to optimise its websites for targeted communication, such as providing information about our products and services.  Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer.  Cookies are used, for instance, to track your preferences for specific websites or to keep lists of favourites.  You can change your browser settings to disable cookies.  However, this may restrict the use of our websites and services.   ** **

 **Links to Other Websites  
** Our communications or websites may contain links to third party websites.   VNU Exhibitions Europe BV is not responsible for the contents of such websites.  

**Changes**   
VNU Exhibitions Europe BV reserves the right to change this privacy statement.  We advise you to check this statement and our website regularly for any changes to this statement. 

**You may access your personal information at any time to have it updated or removed.   Please send a request to this end containing your details to: VNU Exhibitions Europe BV, Databases department, PO Box 8800, 3503 RV Utrecht or send an E-mail to ** [ **privacy@vnuexhibitions.com** ](mailto:privacy@vnuexhibitions.com)
